theluckyladybug.net 2013-05-15

# Privacy Policy - The Lucky Ladybug

This privacy policy is valid from February 17, 2013 and may be changed at any time without notice. This privacy policy is valid for The Lucky Ladybug. Prior posts do not necessarily adhere to this privacy policy. Small changes and additions may be made to this privacy policy without being noted in any special way.

You are encouraged to periodically check back and review this privacy policy so you always will know what information is collected, how it is used, and to whom it is disclosed. Your continued use of The Lucky Ladybug blog following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes.

Gathering and Use  
I respect your privacy and will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information to any third party without first receiving the user’s permission. Personally identifiable information is not collected from visitors other than what is supplied on a voluntary basis. Any personal information you provide here including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and email address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of The Lucky Ladybug.

External Sites  
I am not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

Cookies  
A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows The Lucky Ladybug to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and The Lucky Ladybug does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by third party content providers such as news feeds.

Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet  
While I do my best to protect your personal information, I cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to The Lucky Ladybug and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through The Lucky Ladybug have separate data and independent privacy practices. Therefore, any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions is disclaimed.

Links to other web sites are available for your convenience. The Lucky Ladybug has no control over, does not endorse and is not responsible for the content, advertising, products or other materials on or available from these web sites. Please contact others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

Acceptance  
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. I reserve the right, at my sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

The Lucky Ladybug is a personal blog written and edited by Cheryl, aka The Lucky Ladybug. Feel free to [contact me](http://theluckyladybug.net/contact/) if you have questions about this privacy policy.
